Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXIV. LOCAL LODGES
  - Sub-Series 235-1151. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1151, Waseca, Minnesota, 1921-1953 (Box 141, Folder 2)
      December 30, 1921-February 25, 1953. Membership transferred to and consolidated with Lodge 1163, Chicago, Illinois effective January 1, 1953
  - Sub-Series 235-1154. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1154, Sumter Lodge, Sumter, South Carolina, 1934-1960 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      July 26, 1934-February 16, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 115, Florence, South Carolina effective January 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1155. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1155, Schenectady N.Y. Lodge, Schenectady, New York, 1923-1960 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      April 17, 1923-January 27, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 861, Albany, New York effective January 1, 1960 / Lodge No. 1155, Flying Pilgrim Lodge, Logan International Airport, Boston, Massachusetts
  - Sub-Series 235-1156. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1156, Hub City Mills Lodge, Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada, 1945-1950 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      June 15, 1945-January 30, 1950. Disbanded effective January 30, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-1158. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1158, Dixie Sunshine Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1945-1956 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      July 14, 1945-June 13, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge 901, Beaumont, Texas effective January 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-1159. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1159, C.R.F.C.A. Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1962 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      August 9, 1921-January 19, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge 667, Chicago, Illinois effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1160. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1160, Prescott, Ontario, Canada, 1945-1951 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      October 22, 1945-July 1, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge 1161, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada effective July 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1162. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1162, Sage Brush Lodge, Rawlins/Laramie, Wyoming, 1945-1946 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      October 22, 1945-May 3, 1946. Consolidated with Lodge 93, Green River, Wyoming effective May 3, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-1164. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1164, Patapsco Lodge, Baltimore, Maryland, 1922-1954 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      January 10, 1922-May 7, 1954. Disbanded effective April 6, 1954 / Griffith Lodge, Griffith, Indiana
  - Sub-Series 235-1165. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1165, Rio Santa Lodge, Colorado Springs, Colorado, 1946-1962 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      March 13, 1946-September 24, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge 2014, Colorado Springs, Colorado effective July 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1166. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1166, Frontenac Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1946-1961 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      April 1, 1946-September 29, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge 191, Montreal, Quebec, Canada effective July 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1169. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1169, Waynoka Lodge, Waynoka, Oklahoma, 1921-1951 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      September 20, 1921-March 21, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge 396, Amarillo, Texas effective January 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1173. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1173, Trailways Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1925-1966 (Box 141, Folder 14)
      September 22, 1925-July 1, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge 218, Wichita, Kansas effective July 1, 1966 / Lodge No. 1173, Fort Dodge Lodge, Fort Dodge, Iowa
  - Sub-Series 235-1174. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1174, Pleasant Valley Lodge, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1946-1962 (Box 141, Folder 15)
      May 1, 1946-February 14, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge 980, Kingston, Pennsylvania effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1177. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1177, Roosevelt Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1946-1968 (Box 141, Folder 16)
      May 20, 1946-July 22, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 156, Detroit, Michigan effective July 1, 1968
    - Lodge No. 1177, Geneva Lodge, Geneva, New York, 1921-1930 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      December 22, 1921-December 9, 1930. Disbanded ?
  - Sub-Series 235-1178. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1178, Pennsylvania Railroad Lodge, Youngwood, Pennsylvania, 1930 (Box 141, Folder 18)
      January 10, 1930-April 8, 1930. Disbanded 1930
  - Sub-Series 235-1179. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1179, Deming Lodge, Deming, New Mexico, 1921-1922 (Box 141, Folder 19)
      September 26, 1921-August 15, 1922. Disbanded ?
  - Sub-Series 235-1183. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1183, Pershing Square Lodge, New York, New York, 1948-1960 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      April 22, 1948-February 15, 1960.
    - Lodge No. 1183, Pershing Square Lodge, New York, New York, 1951 (Box 141, Folder 21)
      March 11, 1951-November 25, 1951. Subject: "Charges against and hearing transcript re Charles G. Krouppa"
    - Lodge No. 1183, Bay Area Lodge, San Francisco, California, 1946-1948 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      August 22, 1946-February 17, 1948.
    - Lodge No. 1183, Gulfport Lodge, Gulfport, Mississippi, 1925-1926 (Box 141, Folder 20)
      September 25, 1925-September 20, 1926.
  - Sub-Series 235-1186. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1186, N.Y. Central-Yard Clerks Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1942-1963 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      July 31, 1942-July 25, 1963. Consolidated with Lodge 92 effective April 1, 1963
    - Lodge No. 1186, Catherine Anita Gallagher Lodge, Escanaba, Michigan, 1930-1941 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      December 19, 1930-October 16, 1941. Initiated September 23, 1926, suspended December 31, 1929, reinstated January 1, 1930, consolidated with Lodge 605, Escanaba, Michigan effective July 1, 1941
  - Sub-Series 235-1189. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1189, Lake Shore Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1951 (Box 141, Folder 23)
      May 14, 1951-December 10, 1951. Subject: "Appeal by Mrs. Beulah K. White
    - Lodge No. 1189, Lake Shore Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1921-1961 (Box 141, Folder 24)
      September 7, 1921-April 19, 1961.
    - Lodge No. 95, East Toledo Lodge, East Toledo, Ohio, 1934 (Box 141, Folder 24)
      May 6, 1934-May 7, 1934.
  - Sub-Series 235-1192. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1192, Central General Office Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1922-1948 (Box 141, Folder 25)
      March 20, 1922-August 6, 1948. Location moved from Cleveland, Ohio effective July 7, 1937
  - Sub-Series 235-1194. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1194, Tembar Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1947-1964 (Box 141, Folder 26)
      February 7, 1947-April 17, 1964. Disbanded and members transferred to Lodge 299, Dayton, Ohio, Lodge 567, Baltimore, Maryland and Lodge 1, Cincinnati, Ohio effective April 1, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1195. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1195, St. Lawrence Flour Mills Co. Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1947-1964 (Box 141, Folder 27)
      June 4, 1947-April 6, 1964. Disbanded effective March 31, 1964
  - Sub-Series 235-1197. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1197, Purity Flour Mills Ltd. Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1947-1964 (Box 141, Folder 28)
      August 13, 1947-March 31, 1964.
    - Lodge No. 1197, Avery, Idaho, 1923-1925 (Box 141, Folder 28)
      April 16, 1923-August 27, 1925.
  - Sub-Series 235-1199. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1199, East Cambridge Freight House Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1943-1968 (Box 141, Folder 29)
      September 24, 1943-August 29, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge 119, Boston, Massachusetts effective July 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1201. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1201, Chicago, Illinois, 1947-1960 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      September 10, 1947-January 1, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 342, Chicago, Illinois effective January 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 1201, Wyoming Lodge, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1926-1930 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      April 20, 1926-October 17, 1930. Suspended effective March 31, 1929
    - Lodge No. 1201, Mon Yough Lodge, Duquesne, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      1921 November, 9
    - Lodge No. 1211, Station Employees Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1921 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      August 7, 1921-August 10, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1202. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1202, New Smyrna Lodge, New Smyrna, Florida, 1922-1967 (Box 141, Folder 31)
      April 25, 1922-January 27, 1967. Consolidated with Lodge 848, St. Augustine, Florida effective January 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1203. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1203, NYC Freight Handlers Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1926-1935 (Box 141, Folder 32)
      December 16, 1926-January 1, 1935. Disbanded ?
  - Sub-Series 235-1204. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1204, Gateway Lodge, Smith Falls, Ontario, Canada, 1948-1960 (Box 141, Folder 33)
      March 30, 1948-October 6, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge 39, Smith Falls, Ontario, Canada effective August 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1205. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1205, Murray Hill Lodge, New York, New York, 1947-1957 (Box 141, Folder 34)
      October 27, 1947-October 13, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 235-1207. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1207, Port of Montreal Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1930-1962 (Box 141, Folder 35)
      March 25, 1930-December 4, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 235-1208. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1208, White (Nite) Hawks Lodge, Duluth, Minnesota, 1930-1966 (Box 141, Folder 36)
      July 7, 1930-September 6, 1966. Consolidated with Lodge 319, Duluth, Minnesota effective July 1, 1966
  - Sub-Series 235-1210. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1210, Washington, D.C., 1948-1950 (Box 141, Folder 37)
      March 9, 1948-June 23, 1950. Surrendered charter / suspended effective June 23, 1950
  - Sub-Series 235-1211. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1211, Phoenician Lodge, Phoenix, Arizona, 1948-1962 (Box 141, Folder 38)
      May 13, 1948-November 23, 1962.
    - Lodge No. 1211, Station Employees Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1923-1928 (Box 141, Folder 38)
      July 15, 1923-November 15, 1928. Suspended effective June 30, 1925
  - Sub-Series 235-1212. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1212, Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1921-1957 (Box 141, Folder 39)
      December 4, 1921-April 12, 1957. Moved from St. Paul, Minnesota effective ?
  - Sub-Series 235-1213. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1213, Port Arthur, Ontario, Canada, 1948-1955 (Box 141, Folder 40)
      June 21, 1948-April 1, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1446, no location given, effective April 1, 1955
    - Lodge No. 1213, Sweetwater, Texas, 1922 (Box 141, Folder 40)
      1922 September 22
  - Sub-Series 235-1215. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1215, Rochester Lodge, Rochester, New York, 1926-1959 (Box 141, Folder 41)
      December 16, 1926-October 15, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-1217. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1217, Humber Lodge, Corner Brook, Newfoundland, Canada, 1948-1950 (Box 141, Folder 42)
      September 7, 1948-October 1, 1950. Consolidated with Lodge No. 443, St. John's, Newfoundland, Canada, effective October 1, 1950
    - Lodge No. 1217, East Toledo Lodge, East Toledo, Ohio, 1929-1930 (Box 141, Folder 42)
      October 31, 1929-May 1, 1930.
  - Sub-Series 235-1218. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1218, Bogalusa Lodge, Bogalusa, Louisiana, 1930-1932 (Box 141, Folder 43)
      January 11, 1930-June 6, 1932. Suspended, effective June 3, 1932
  - Sub-Series 235-1219. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1219, Baltimore and Ohio Lodge, Garrett, Indiana, 1949-1965 (Box 141, Folder 44)
      May 20, 1949-September 10, 1965. Consolidated with Lodge No. 114, Willard, Ohio, effective July 1, 1965
    - Lodge No. 1219, Genesee Valley Lodge, Rochester, New York, 1922-1932 (Box 141, Folder 44)
      April 5, 1922-November 1, 1932. Suspended, effective September 30, 1932
  - Sub-Series 235-1222. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1222, Racine, Wisconsin, 1949-1951 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      May 27, 1949-October 30, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 231, Green Bay, Wisconsin; Lodge No. 606, Madison, Wisconsin; and Lodge No. 675, Chicago, Illinois; effective October 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1225. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1225, Columbia Lodge, Columbia, South Carolina, 1943-1960 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      April 8, 1943-February 5, 1960. Consolidated with Lodge No. 115, Florence, South Carolina, effective January 1, 1960
    - Lodge No. 1225, Chadron, Nebraska, 1926-1943 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      February 1, 1926-February 18, 1943. Suspended, effective February 18, 1943
  - Sub-Series 235-1226. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1226, River Street Lodge, Newark, New Jersey, 1922-1923 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      September 4, 1922-April 18, 1923. Suspended, effective March 31, 1923
  - Sub-Series 235-1228. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1228, Perth Amboy Lodge, Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1922-1923 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      January 24, 1922-November 19, 1923. Suspended, effective September 30, 1923
  - Sub-Series 235-1229. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1229, Allen Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1921-1961 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      December 9, 1921-December 12, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 235-1231. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1231, Portage Lodge, Portage, Wisconsin, 1953-1962 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      May 25, 1953-May 25, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 606, Madison, Wisconsin, effective April 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 1231, Sunshine Lodge, St. Petersburg, Florida, 1928 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      July 12, 1928-August 25, 1928.
    - Lodge No. 1231, East Vaughn, New Mexico, 1922 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      March 16, 1922-April 5, 1922.(?)
  - Sub-Series 235-1233. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1233, Milwaukee Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1924-1962 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      January 2, 1924-November 15, 1962. Formerly Victory Lodge
  - Sub-Series 235-1235. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1235, Pioneer Lodge, West Springfield, Massachusetts, 1928-1956 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      December 5, 1928-June 1, 1956. Consolidated with Lodge No. 336, Lodge No. 460, and Lodge No. 1517, Springfield, Massachusetts, effective January 1, 1956
  - Sub-Series 235-1236. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1236, Renovo Lodge, Renovo, Pennsylvania, 1949-1955 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      September 27, 1949-February 3, 1955. Consolidated with Lodge No. 664, Williamsport, Pennsylvania, effective January 1, 1955
  - Sub-Series 235-1237. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1237, Steamship Checkers Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1921-1927 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      March 11, 1921-April 6, 1927. Disbanded?
    - Lodge No. 1237, Calumet Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1949-1968 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      October 18, 1949-March 7, 1968. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1102, Chicago, Illinois, effective January 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1239. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1239, Chinook Lodge, Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1949-1958 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      November 4, 1949-December 30, 1958. Disbanded, effective September 30, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-1240. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1240, Ann Arbor Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1926-1931 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      December 21, 1926-January 29, 1931. Suspended, effective June 30, 1929
  - Sub-Series 235-1242. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1242, Streamliner Lodge, Ashland, Wisconsin, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      February 28, 1950-May 1, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 605, Escanaba, Michigan, effective April 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 1242, Abanda Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1921 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      1921 December 29
  - Sub-Series 235-1243. Local Lodges
    - Lode No. 1243, Crystal City Lodge, Corning, New York, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 15)
      March 27, 1950-January 30, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 658, Elmira, New York, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1244. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1244, Grand Junction Lodge, East Boston, Massachusetts, 1950-1967 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      March 17, 1950-March 28, 1967. Consolidated with Lodge No. 230, Boston, Massachusetts, effective January 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1245. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1245, Highline Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1924-1967 (Box 142, Folder 17)
      September 15, 1924-July 18, 1967. Moved from Edgemont, South Dakota, effective 1924; consolidated with Lodge No. 921, Kansas City, Missouri, effective April 1, 1967
  - Sub-Series 235-1246. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1246, Tom Sykes Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      March 7, 1950-April 10, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1590, East St. Louis, Illinois, effective April 1, 1962
    - Lodge No. 1246, Keystone Lodge, Toledo, Ohio, 1922 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      November 3-7, 1922.
  - Sub-Series 235-1247. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1247, Chester Lodge, Chester, South Carolina, 1921-1942 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      January 8, 1921-October 15, 1942. Consolidated with Lodge No. 522, Atlanta, Georgia, effective October 15, 1942
  - Sub-Series 235-1249. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1249, Leewood Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1950-1952 (Box 142, Folder 20)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1281, Clarksville, Tennessee; Lodge No. 407, Louisville, Kentucky; Lodge No. 297, Memphis, Tennessee effective Oct. 1, 1951
    - Lodge No. 1249, Queen City of the Lakes Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1921-1922 (Box 142, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 235-1252. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1252, Washington Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1950-1968 (Box 142, Folder 21)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1265, New York City, New York, effective April 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1253. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1253, Boston Pullman Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts, 1950-1961 (Box 142, Folder 22)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1345, Chicago, Illinois, effective Jan. 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1254. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1254, Kansas City Terminal Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1921-1959 (Box 142, Folder 23)
      1921-Feb. 13, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 235-1255. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1255, Niagara Frontier Lodge, Buffalo, New York, 1950-1959 (Box 142, Folder 24)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1345, Chicago, Illinois, effective Dec. 31, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-1256. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1256, Rock Island Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1935-1946 (Box 142, Folder 25)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1266, Blue Island, Illinois effective Sept. 28, 1946
  - Sub-Series 235-1258. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1258, Atlanta Pullman Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1950-1961 (Box 142, Folder 26)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 956, Atlanta, Georgia, effective April 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1258, Missouri Valley Iowa Lodge, Missouri Valley, Iowa, 1922-1929 (Box 142, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 235-1259. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1259, Colorado-Utah Pullman Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 27)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1270, St. Louis, Missouri effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1261. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1261, Golden West Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 28)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1345, Chicago, Illinois, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1262. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1262, Especo Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1921-1957 (Box 142, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 235-1267. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1267, Angus Stores Lodge, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1921-1963 (Box 142, Folder 30)
      1921-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 235-1268. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1268, Grand Haven Lodge, New York, New York, 1950-1968 (Box 142, Folder 31)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1265, New York, New York, effective April 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1269. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1269, Prairie Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1929-1963 (Box 142, Folder 32)
      March 30, 1929-March 15, 1963. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1029, Chicago, Illinois, effective January 1, 1963
    - Lodge No. 1269, Prairie Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1941-1944 (Box 142, Folder 33)
      October 7, 1941-February 25, 1944. Subject: "Jurisdiction Lodges Nos. 604, 1029, 1269"
  - Sub-Series 235-1270. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1270, Missouri Pullman Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1950-1968 (Box 142, Folder 34)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 1102, Chicago, Illinois, effective Oct. 1, 1968
  - Sub-Series 235-1271. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1271, Florida Lodge, Miami, Florida, 1950-1960 (Box 142, Folder 35)
      March 3, 1950-October 18, 1960. Moved from Jacksonville, Florida, effective March 6, 1953; consolidated with Lodge No. 1345, Chicago, Illinois, effective October 1, 1960
  - Sub-Series 235-1273. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1273, Kansas City Pullman Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1950-1961 (Box 142, Folder 36)
      May 10, 1950-May 5, 1961. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1270, St. Louis, Missouri, effective April 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1273, Lechmere Lodge, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1927 (Box 142, Folder 36)
      September 23, 1927-November 18, 1927. Disbanded, effective September 11, 1927
  - Sub-Series 235-1274. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1274, Proviso Lodge, Proviso, Illinois, 1930-1962 (Box 142, Folder 37)
      June 30, 1930-April 24, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 679, Chicago, Illinois, effective April 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1276. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1276, Phil-Wil Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1950-1962 (Box 142, Folder 38)
      May 23, 1950-February 27, 1962. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1265, New York, New York, effective January 1, 1962
  - Sub-Series 235-1277. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1277, Bay Ridge Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1922-1926 (Box 142, Folder 39)
      May 5, 1922-July 12, 1926. Consolidated with Lodge No. 2125, no location or date given
  - Sub-Series 235-1279. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1279, Pullman Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1950-1951 (Box 142, Folder 40)
      October 2, 1950-July 1, 1951. Consolidated with Lodge No. 1270, St. Louis, Missouri, effective July 1, 1951
  - Sub-Series 235-1281. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1281, Memphis Line Lodge, Paris, Tennessee, 1931-1961 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 297, Memphis, Tennessee, effective Oct. 1, 1961
  - Sub-Series 235-1282. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1282, Pitcairn Stores Lodge, Pitcairn, Pennsylvania, 1922-1958 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 729, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, effective July 1, 1958
  - Sub-Series 235-1284. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1284, Claude Anderack Lodge, Sherman, Texas, 1950-1961 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 131, Fort Worth, Texas, effective Jan. 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1284, Flora Lodge, Flora, Illinois, 1921 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      Aug. 1921.
  - Sub-Series 235-1286. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1286, Boston and Maine Freight Handlers Lodge, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 143, Folder 4)
      Disbanded, effective September 30, 1943
  - Sub-Series 235-1289. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1289, Woodgate Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1951-1961 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      Consolidated with Lodge No. 549, Chicago, Illinois, effective April 1, 1961
    - Lodge No. 1289, El Dorado, Arkansas, 1922-1923 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 235-1298. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1298, Cleveland Station Employees Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1952-1958 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      May, 1952-December 31, 1958.
    - Lodge No. 1298, Cleveland Station Employees Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1923-1952 (Box 143, Folder 7)
      November 2, 1923-April 2, 1952.
  - Sub-Series 235-1300. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1300, Alavie Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1921-1924 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      October 29, 1921-January 29, 1924. Disbanded?
  - Sub-Series 235-1302. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1302, Old Allegheny Lodge, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1951-1953 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      May 21, 1951-January 27, 1953. Consolidated with Lodge No. 608, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, effective January 1, 1953
    - Lodge No. 1302, Keystone Freight Handlers Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1922-1932 (Box 143, Folder 9)
      March 6, 1922-July 5, 1932.
  - Sub-Series 235-1303. Local Lodges
    - Lodge No. 1303, Tie Plant Lodge, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1951-1952 (Box 143, Folder 10)